RG 041:002, Public Utilities Commission
Connecticut State Library
- Series 5. Dockets, 1911-1988; 135.75 cubic feet
  - Accession: 1985-009, 1939-1980
    - Conn. Railway and Lighting Co. - increase fares, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11272)
    - Greenwich Taxi, Inc. - increase in taxi cab rates of fares, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11273)
    - The Orange St. Bus Line, Inc. of New Haven - to discontinue Saturday evening service, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11283)
    - The Conn. Co. - to increase motor bus fares in the Stamford division, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11295)
    - Darien Taxi and Limousine, Inc. - increase in taxi cab fares, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11296)
    - The Norwich City Cab Co. - to discontinue bus service in Norwich, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11306)
    - National Bus Traffic Association, Inc. - Agent for Greyhound Lines, Inc. of Cleveland, Ohio - to increase interstate fares Lines, Inc. of Cleveland, Ohio - to increase intrastate fares, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11316)
    - Orange Street Bus Line, Inc. of New Haven - increase in bus fares, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11331)
    - Arthur Lord, DBA Bloomfield - Windsor Cab - increase in taxi cab fares, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11345)
    - Citation to Conn. Railway and Lighting Co. - Failure to operate service under certificate no. 219, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11353)
    - Savin Bus Lines of New London - to discontinue service within New London and Waterford, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11381)
    - Corbin Coach Line, Inc. of New Britain - increase bus rates of fares, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11382)
    - Barstow Transportation of Dayville - increase in fares, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11391)
    - Stamford Taxi, Inc. - to change from meter to zone fares, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11412)
    - North East Transportation Co., Inc. - Bus Fare Equalization, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11453)
    - Darien Taxi and Limousine, Inc. - increase in taxi cab fares, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11468)
    - New London Taxi Cab Operators - fare increase, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11469)
    - Valley Transit district - Citation for operation beyond Authorized Area, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11472)
    - Yellow Cab Co. of Hartford - increase in fares, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11488)
    - Stratford Bus Line - increase in fare, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11492)
    - For Transportation of non-emergency patients by taxi cab with attendant, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11504)
    - Yellow Cab Co., Inc. of Middletown - fare increase, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11506)
    - Kenneth F. Andrews, DBA City Cab of Putnam - fare increase, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11515)
    - Central Conn. Limousine Service, Inc. - fare increase, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11516)
    - Wilton Taxi Service, Inc. - increase in fares, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11522)
    - Terminal Taxi Cab, DBA Yellow Cab (New Haven) increase fares, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11523)
    - The Edward P. Hayes & Sons Co. - Discontinue Meriden to Middletown Bus Service, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11527)
    - Joseph H. McMahon Transportation Co. - Discontinue all Bus Service in Meriden, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11528)
    - The Town Taxi Company (Stratford) - fare increase, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11530)
    - Empire Bus Lines, Inc. - Investigation of various violations of General Statutes and Commission Regulations, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11536)
    - Trumbull Cab Company - fare increase, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11537)
    - Greenwich Taxi, Inc. - fare increase, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11547)
    - Stamford Taxi, Inc. - fare increase, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11548)
    - Old Lyme - Saybrook Taxi, Inc. - fare increase, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11557)
    - David Haynes, DBA West Side Taxi - Change from meter fares to zone fares, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11570)
    - Beebe Transit Co. - increase in bus fares, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11572)
    - The Norwich City Cab Co. - increase fares, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11577)
    - New London & Groton Taxi Cab Operators - fare increase, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11583)
    - Hickey Cab Co., Inc. - increase in fares, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11618)
    - Branford Cab, Inc. - increase in rates, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11642)
    - Yellow Cab Co. of New London & Groton, Inc. - increase fares, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11683)
    - The New Britain Transportation Co. - Discontinuance of portion of authority, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11653)
    - David's Bus Service, Inc. - Discontinuance of Bus Service in from North Branford to New Haven, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 11685)
    - Chestnut Hill Bus Corp. - Appeal from Decision of the Greater Decision of the Greater Bridgeport Transit District, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11689)
    - The Airfield Service Co. - Ament Bus Fares, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11692)
    - Central Conn. Limousine Service, Inc. - Abandon a portion of it's Motor Bus Service, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11700)
    - The Yellow Cab Co. of Hartford - increase fares, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11722)
    - The Short Line of Conn., Inc. - increase bus fares, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11761)
    - The Airfield Service Co. - increase bus fares, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11771)
    - The Orange St. Bus Line Co., Inc. - increase fares, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11774)
    - Central Conn. Limousine Service, Inc. - increase fares, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 11780)
    - Manchester Ice & Fuel, Inc. - Investigation and suspension no. 122, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 11797)
    - National Bus Traffic Assoc., Inc. (Bonanza, Chieppo, Greyhound Lines) - fare increase, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 751204)
    - PUCA - Proposal to Amend Regulations concerning Buses operated in Livery Service, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 751205)
    - The Terminal Taxi Co. Yellow Cab of New Haven - Rates of Fare, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 760201)
    - New Britain Transportation Co. - Fare increase, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 760205)
    - Town & Country Cab, Inc., New Britain - Resolve complaints from the General Public, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 760501)
    - The East Hartford Cab Co. - Rates of Fare increase, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 760603)
    - General hearing to discuss the suitability of van type vehicles in taxi cab service, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 760609)
    - New London Area Taxi Co's - increase in rates of fare (6 companies), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 770516)
    - Barstow Transp. - Petition for new fares, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 770517)
    - Eastern Bus Lines - Complaints, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 770604)
    - The Arrow Line, Inc. - Discontinue portion of Service, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 770605)
    - Eastern Bus Service to P & W Aircraft in East Hartford - Investigation of Complaints, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 770609)
    - Central Conn. Limousine Service, Inc. - rate increase, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 770923)
    - Terminal Taxi - increase in fares, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 771022)
    - Dickaw Bus Co., Inc. - rate increase, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 780101)
    - Longueil Transportation, Inc. - fare increase, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 780404)
    - The Waterbury Yellow Cab & Service Co. - Amend rates of fares in Waterbury and Watertown Waterbury and Watertown, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 780414)
    - Arthur J. Castellucci, DBA Fairfield Cab Co. - Emergency Interim Rate Increase, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 780512)
    - PUCA - Investigation Regarding Authorization of a 'service Charge" on Unpaid Balance of Taxi and Livery Operators Billings Unpaid Balance of Taxi and Livery Operators Billings, 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 780514)
    - Stamford Taxi, Inc. - increase in rates, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 780609)
    - Greenwich Taxi, Inc. - increase in rates, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 780610)
    - PUCA - Investigation Accessorial charge of assisting persons to and from taxi and Livery Vehicles, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 780615)
    - The Blue Line, Inc. - increase in fares, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 780628)
    - Town & Country Yellow Cab - rate increase, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 780636)
    - Meriden Yellow Cab - Shared Ride Program - Meriden, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 780641)
    - Carolyn's Checker Cab Co. - Shared Rides - New Haven Area, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 780642)
    - Yellow Cab Co. - Hartford - Shared Ride Service, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 780643)
    - Petition of Dattco, Inc. - Bus Service - Knapp Village - New Britain, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 780713)
    - Yellow Cab Co. of Hartford, Inc. - increase in fares, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 780910)
    - New Britain Transportation - Discontinue Bus Service on Sat. - Corbin Avenue, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 780913)
    - Petition of the Union-Lyceum Taxi Co., DBA Blue Cab Co. Groton Cab Co., Inc. and the Yellow Cab Co. of New London and Groton, Inc. - Authorization to increase its taxi cab fares within New London and Groton, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 789014)
    - National Bus Traffic Assoc., Inc. - increase in Conn. Interstate Passenger fares, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 780927)
    - Stanley Barstow, DBA Barstow Transp. - increase in fares, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 780929)
    - The Blue Line, Inc. - Temporary Suspension, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 781011)
    - Petition of Mayor of New Britain - Service - Martin Luther King Drive, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 781113)
    - National Bus Traffic Assoc., Inc. - increase in fares, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 781121)
    - Plainville Cab Co. - fare increase, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 781212)
    - The Chieppo Bus Co. - Abandon all interstate Motor Bus Service, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 781213)
    - Old Lyme - Saybrook Taxi Service, Inc. - increase in fares, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 790203)
    - Petition of; Groton Cab Co., Inc.; The Union Lyceum Taxi Co., DBA Blue Cab Co; The Yellow Cab of New London & Groton, DBA Yellow Cab Co. shared ride taxi service in New London, Groton area Cab Co. Shared ride taxi service in New London, Groton area, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 790206)
    - Adoption of Regulations for Shared - Ride Taxi Cab Service, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 790208)
    - The Blue Line, Inc. - increase in fares, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 790211)
    - Easter Bus Lines, Inc. - increase in fares, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790303)
    - The Chieppo Bus Co. - Restructuring Regular Routes and increase in fares, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790314)
    - Denise, Inc., DBA Travel Time - increase in fares, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790401)
    - Arrow Line, Inc. - Reduce Service, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 790412)
    - Eugene M. Singer, DBA Branford Cab - fare increase, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790507)
    - Travel Time - Discontinue Service - Pratt & Whitney, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790518)
    - Easter Bus Lines, Inc. - Discontinue Portion of Service, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790519)
    - Taxi Cab Operators in Conn. - Consideration of Rate relief, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790526)
    - Yellow Cab Co. - fare increase - (Torrington & Winsted), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790607)
    - Central Conn. Limousine Service, Inc. - Valley & Groton runs to Bradley Field, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790613)
    - Central Conn. Limousine Service, Inc. - Group Rate fares to Bradley Field, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790614)
    - PUCA - Proposal Regulations - Pkg Carriage on Motor Buses (Sec. 20 A-G), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790621)
    - New Britain Transportation Coalition - Dattco - Service Senior Citizens Center, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 790622)
    - Southington Taxi, Inc. - fare increase, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 790813)
    - Short Line of Conn., Inc. - New Haven/Hartford Reg. Route - Cut Service, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 790824)
    - Corbin Coach Lines, Inc. - Discontinue Service on Sat. & Sun. over Hartford - Waterbury Route, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 760306)
    - The Orange St. Bus Line, Inc. - Reduce present fare of 35@ to senior citizens & 150 to handicapped citizens, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 760310)
    - Chestnut Hill Bus Corp. - rate increase, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 760402)
    - Bridgeport Auto Transit Co. - Appeal of Greater Bridgeport Transit Dist., 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 760403)
    - Dattco, Inc. - Reduced Rates for Senior Citizens, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 760408)
    - Stanley S. Barstow, DBA Barstow Transportation - rate increase, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 760606)
    - Eastern Bus Lines, Inc. - increase in fares, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 760608)
    - Corbin Coach Lines, Inc. - Proposed rate schedule for Old Saybrook to Electric Boat in Groton, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 770106)
    - PUCA - Amend Regs. - Re Taxi Cab & Livery Service, 1977-1979 (Box 16, Folder 770214)
    - Clinton - Madison Taxi - rate increase, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 770307)
    - PUCA - Bus Service to Dog Tracks, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 770308)
    - Ridgefield Taxi, Inc. - increase in rates of fare, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 770317)
    - Meriden Yellow Cab Co. - Request to Raise Rates of Fare, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 770325)
    - Waterbury Yellow Cab and Service Co., Inc. - Rate Request, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 770420)
    - PUCA Investigation on complaints of Short Line of Conn., Inc. concerning unauthorized operations of Park City Coach Re: Service to Electric Boat in Groton to Electric Boat in Groton, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 770432)
    - Francis A. Brooks, DBA Arrow Cab Service - fares increase, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 770809)
    - The Connecticut Company, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3025)
    - The Conn. Co., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3026)
    - The Conn. Co., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3027)
    - The Conn. Co., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3029)
    - Airfield Ser. Co., Inc. of Htfd., CT - Authority to operate motor bus service between Hartford & Windsor Locks (Bradley Field), 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3031)
    - Antonia Lusa, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3059)
    - Bristol Traction Co., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3062)
    - The Conn. Co., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3063)
    - New England Transportation Co., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3065)
    - Cooke St. Line, Inc., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3073)
    - The Conn. Co, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3078)
    - The Conn. Co., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3079)
    - Roy J. Rodriguez, Plainville, CT, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3082)
    - Lionel Leclair, Naugatuck, CT, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3091)
    - E.J. Kelley (Cherry Park), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3102)
    - E.J. Kelley Co. (Lake Compound), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3103)
    - E.J. Kelley Co. (Yale Bowl Arena, Savin Rock in West Haven, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3104)
    - E. J. Kelley Co. (Highland Lake), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3105)
    - E.J. Kelley Co. (ext. of local route ), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3106)
    - E.J. Kelley Co. (authority to operate bus service to the Goshen Harwinton & Danbury Fairs), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3107)
    - The White Line Bus Corp. of Bridgeport, CT., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3108)
    - Trumbull Coach Lines, Inc. of Trumbull, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3117)
    - Trumbull Coach Lines, Inc. of Trumbull, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3118)
    - The Arrow Line - Lakeland Transp. Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3124)
    - The Arrow Line - Lakeland Transp. Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3124A)
    - The Arrow Line - Lakeland Transp. Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3156)
    - Central Bus Corp. - Conn. Railway and Lighting Co., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3174)
    - Central Bus Corp. - Conn. Railway and Lighting Co., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 3190)
    - Residents of the Town of Stratford - Bus service by The Conn. Railway and Lighting Co. along South Avenue and South Main Street South Main Street, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 3225)
    - Theodore E. Wagner, New Britain, CT., 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 3249)
    - Corbin Ave. Bus Service, New Britain, Ct., 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 3250)
    - Waterbury Yellow Cab & Service Co. - increase rates for Waterbury taxicab operators, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11121)
    - Chestnut Hill Bus Corporation - discontinue evening service on its Madison Avenue - Trumbull Route, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11124)
    - Yellow Cab of Bristol, Inc. - to increase taxicab fares, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11126)
    - City of Hartford - Suitability of Conn. company for acquisition by the Greater Hartford Transit District, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11139)
    - Connecticut Railway & Lighting Company - curtailment of service in New Britain, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11140)
    - Newington Taxi Service, Inc. - to increase fares, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11142)
    - The New Britain Transportation Co. - to increase bus fares in New Britain, Bristol and Plainville, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11143)
    - The Blue Line, Inc. of Windham - to increase bus fares in New Britain, Bristol and Plainville, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11157)
    - The Blue Line, Inc. of Windham - to increase motor bus fares, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11157)
    - The Conn. Co. - to discontinue service in its Stamford division, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11168)
    - The Conn. Railway & Lighting Co. of Bridgeport - Milford curtailment, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11172)
    - Gray Line Bus Co. of Bridgeport - reduce bus service, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11186)
    - The Norwich City Cab Co. - to increase taxicab fares, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11188)
    - Gray Line Bus Co. - to reduce bus service, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11201)
    - Docket index cards, A-L (Box 19)
    - Docket index cards, M-Y, State (Box 20)
  - Accession: 2011-101, 1911-1988, bulk 1911-1932
    Rail, bus, livery and trucking dockets.
    Not every docket is present within the given range of numbers.
    - 87-01-08 - 88-10-08 (Box 1)
    - 8092-8674 (Box 2)
    - 4177-4989, 8425-8815 (Box 3)
    - 7-211, 1306-1346 (Box 4)
    - 381-493, 4088-4148 (Box 5)
    - 495-629, 1257-1291 (Box 6)
    - 639-761, 2056-2070, 8552-8558 (Box 7)
    - 763-893, 8748-8773 (Box 8)
    - 1034-1150, 2082-2146, 2677-2709 (Box 9)
    - 1350-1439 (Box 10)
    - 1471-1595, 5636-5665, 8679-8700 (Box 11)
    - 1441-1446, 1708-1780, 1891-1938, 10700, 10713, 10727, 10727, 82-11-02 (Box 12)
    - 1946-2055, 8560-8587 (Box 13)
    - 2071-2456 (Box 14)
    - 1826-1890, 2551-2626, 10921, 10921-A (Box 15)
    - 2710-2918, 3599-3637, 5667-5699, 8399-8417 (Box 16)
    - 3093-3280, 5221-5294, 8782 (Box 17)
    - 2084-2092, 3472-3535, 9901-10888 (Box 18)
    - 3991-4087, 8459-8500, 10878-10879 (Box 19)
    - 4149-4168, 4679-4729, 5391-5470 (Box 20)
    - 4266-4345 (Box 21)
    - 4346-4420, 8274-8309 (Box 22)
    - 3638-3762, 4423-4495, 8742 (Box 23)
    - 4496-4713, 8674 (Box 24)
    - 3536-3598, 4733-4817 (Box 25)
    - 4823-4927 (Box 26)
    - 4190-4264, 5105-5209 (Box 27)
    - 3425-3456, 5212-5220, 5701-5774, 10662-10666 (Box 28)
    - 1744-1813, 5301-5390 (Box 29)
    - 1601-1705, 5596-5634, 5886, 10900-10905 (Box 30)
    - Applications, B8386-B8474, 1948 July 30 - 1961 January 25 (Box 31)
- Series 6. Daily Log Books, 1948-1976; 6 cubic feet (35 volumes); 1997-061
  Records hearings held and documents issued.
  There are 2 volumes for 1948, 1958, 1971, 1973, 1974, 1975.
- Series 7. Miscellaneous Records, 1911-1924; .5 cubic feet; 1932-075 except where noted
  Includes correspondence, petitions, and reports.
  - Records, 1911-1924 (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
  - Untitled book, circa 1911 (Box 1)
    The list below is taken from the Contents sheets at the end of the volume.
    - Matters relating to railroad and street railway companies (Box 1)
      - Connecticut laws (Box 1)
        Sheets 2-32.
      - United States laws (Box 1)
        Sheets 33-47.
      - Rhode Island laws (Box 1)
        Sheets 48-61.
      - Massachusetts laws (Box 1)
        Sheets 62-119.
      - New York public service commissions laws (Box 1)
        Sheets 120-127.
      - Statistics showing proportion of inter-state to intra-state tonnage carried by the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad in the months of July 1907 and January 1908 (Box 1)
        Sheets 128.
      - Comparative statistics of railroad rates (Box 1)
        Sheets 129-130.
      - Consolidations of Connecticut street railway companies (Box 1)
        Sheets 131-134.
      - Draft of an Act Concerning Mortgage Bonds of Railroad and Railway Companies (Box 1)
        Sheets 135-136.
      - Draft of an Act Concerning the Taking of Land by Railway Companies (Box 1)
        Sheets 137-138.
    - Matters relating to gas and electric light companies (Box 1)
      - Connecticut laws (Box 1)
        Sheets 1002-1009.
      - Massachusetts laws (Box 1)
        Sheets 1010-1026.
      - New York public service commissions laws (Box 1)
        Sheets 1027-1030.
      - Charters of electric light or power companies (Box 1)
        Sheets 1031-1045.
      - Questions asked of gas and electric lighting or power companies in Connecticut (Box 1)
        Sheets 1046-1047.
      - Tabulated returns of gas companies (Box 1)
        Sheets 1048-1058.
      - Tabulated returns of electric light or power companies (Box 1)
      - Late return of Hartford Electric Light Company (Box 1)
        Sheet 1073.
      - Tabulated comparison of capitalization and rates. Massachusetts and Connecticut gas companies (Box 1)
        Sheets 1074-1075.
      - Tabulated comparison of capitalization and rates of Massachusetts and Connecticut electric light companies (Box 1)
        Sheets 1076-1077.
      - Late return of Wallingford Gas Light Company (Box 1)
        Sheet 1078.
    - Matters relating to telephone and telegraph companies (Box 1)
      - Connecticut laws (Box 1)
        Pages 2002-2007.
      - Report of the Board of Directors and Legislative Committee of the State Business Men's Association (Box 1)
        Sheets 2008-2017.
      - The Southern New England Telephone Company, stock statement (Box 1)
        Sheets 2018-1019.
      - Data concerning the provisions of rural telephone service by the Southern New England telephone Company (Box 1)
        Sheets 2020-2037.
      - Table showing growth of exchanges and stations of Southern New England Telephone Company (Box 1)
        Sheet 2038.
      - Statement of advantages to the Southern New England Telephone Company resulting from its contract relationship with the American Telephone and Telegraph Company (Box 1)
        Sheets 2039-2042.
      - Standard rates of the Southern New England Telephone Company (Box 1)
        Sheets 2043-2048.
      - Statistics of telephones as taken from the special report of telephones and telegraphs published by the Census Office for the year 1902 (Box 1)
        Sheets 2049-2050.
    - Matters relating to water companies (Box 1)
      - Questions asked of water companies in Connecticut (Box 1)
        Sheet 3002.
      - Tabulated returns of water companies (Box 1)
        Sheets 3003-3009.
    - Miscellaneous matter (Box 1)
      - Report of hearing March 9, 1908 (Box 1)
        Sheets 4001-4037.
      - Report of hearing April 6, 1908 (Box 1)
        Sheets 4038-4052.
      - Instance illustrating abuse of franchise rights, submitted by Hartford-Middletown trolley committee (Box 1)
        Sheets 4053-4066.
      - Resolution of the Willimantic Business Men's Association (Box 1)
        Sheets 4067-4068.
      - Abstract of President Wilson's Address before The Commercial Club of Chicago, march 14, 1908, submitte dby mr. Travis of New Haven (Box 1)
        Sheets 4069-4074.
      - Letter from Samuel Keeler, Director of State Business Men's Association of Connecticut (Box 1)
        Sheets 4075.
      - Letter from Meriden Business Men's Association (Box 1)
        Sheets 4076.
      - Letter from State Business Men's Association (Box 1)
        Sheets 4077.
      - List of Connecticut towns showing lighting and water companies actively operating in each (Box 1)
        Sheets 4078-4080.
      - Minutes of Commission meeting, July 8, 1908 (Box 1)
  - Charts Showing Electric Utilities and Constituent Companies / Prepared for the Public Utilities Commission by Edward Field, Auditor and Statistician, 1923 January 1; 1 volume (2 cubic feet); T003306 (Volume Item 1)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission Stenographer's Minutes, 2014-021; .5 cubic feet (3 volumes)
    - Investigation of the derailment of the second section of train no. 53, upon the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad at Westport, Connecticut, October 3rd, 1912. At Waldorf-Astoria, New York City, 1912 October 8; 1 volume (Volume Item 1)